Everyone, please think
请大家想想
of your biggest personal goal.
你们最大的人生目标。
For real -- you can take a second. You've got to feel this to learn it.
实际的人生目标。你得想一会儿。你有感觉知道你的目标。
Take a few seconds and think of your personal biggest goal, okay?
花几秒钟想想人生最大的目标，好么？
Imagine deciding right now
想象一下，立马做出决定
that you're going to do it.
你将要做的事情。
Imagine telling someone that you meet today what you're going to do.
想象一下，告诉你今天遇到的人你将要做什么
Imagine their congratulations
想象他们的祝贺
and their high image of you.
和你在他们眼中的英伟形象。
Doesn't it feel good to say it out loud?
大声说出来是不是十分爽？
Don't you feel one step closer already,
你是不是觉得更进一步了
like it's already becoming part of your identity?
貌似这已经成为你自己的一部分？
Well, bad news: you should have kept your mouth shut,
嗯，坏消息：你最好闭嘴，
because that good feeling
因为你的自我感觉良好，
now will make you less likely to do it.
在现实中反而使你不太容易实现目标。
Repeated psychology tests have proven
许多心理测试已证明
that telling someone your goal
告诉别人你的目标
makes it less likely to happen.
反而使目标不能实现。
Any time you have a goal,
任何时候在你有个目标时，
there are some steps that need to be done, some work that needs to be done
你得按计划做些工作
in order to achieve it.
来实现这个目标。
Ideally, you would not be satisfied until you had actually done the work.
理想状况下，除非你实际地做些工作，你才会满足，
But when you tell someone your goal and they acknowledge it,
但是当你告诉别人你的目标，大家也承认你的目标，
psychologists have found that it's called a "social reality."
心理学家发现，这被称为一种社会现实。
The mind is kind of tricked into feeling that it's already done.
思维定势让你有种感觉到你的目标已经达到。
And then, because you felt that satisfaction,
然后，因为你感到满足感，
you're less motivated to do
你不那么积极地做
the actual hard work necessary. (Laughter)
实际需要的艰苦工作。
So this goes against the conventional wisdom
这观点和传统观点背道而驰，
that we should tell our friends our goals, right --
我们应该告诉我们朋友们关于我们的目标吗，对吗？
so they hold us to it.
他们鼓励我们实现目标，对。
So, let's look at the proof.
我们来看看这个证明。
1926, Kurt Lewin, founder of social psychology,
1926年，社会心理学的创始人库尔特·勒温
called this "substitution."
称这个为“替代”。
1933, Vera Mahler found,
1933年，伟拉马勒发现
when it was acknowledged by others, it felt real in the mind.
当你的目标被别人承认，在你脑子里就好比这已经实现了。
1982, Peter Gollwitzer wrote a whole book about this
1982年，皮特哥尔维策尔关于此写了一本书，
and in 2009,
在2009年，
he did some new tests that were published.
他公布了一些新的实验证明。
It goes like this:
比如这个：
163 people across four separate tests --
163个人进行4组不同测试--
everyone wrote down their personal goal.
每个人写下他们各自的目标，
Then half of them announced their commitment to this goal to the room,
然后一半实验的人在房间里宣布他们的目标承诺，
and half didn't.
另一半人保守目标。
Then everyone was given 45 minutes of work
接下来每个人有45分钟来工作，
that would directly lead them towards their goal,
他们可以努力工作直至实现他们的目标，
but they were told that they could stop at any time.
但他们在任何时候也可以停下来工作。
Now, those who kept their mouths shut
那些不泄漏目标的人
worked the entire 45 minutes, on average,
平均工作了整整45分钟，
and when asked afterwards,
在这之后的访问，
said that they felt that they had a long way to go still to achieve their goal.
他们感到他们为了实现目标还有很长的一段路要走。
But those who had announced it
但是那些宣布目标的人们
quit after only 33 minutes, on average,
平均工作大约33分钟后就放弃了，
and when asked afterwards,
当被问及时，
said that they felt much closer to achieving their goal.
他们感到快要接近目标了。
So, if this is true,
所以如果这是事实，
what can we do?
我们会怎样做？
Well, you could resist the temptation
好吧，大家可以抵制住
to announce your goal.
宣布目标的诱惑。
You can delay the gratification
大家可以延迟这种
that the social acknowledgement brings,
社交承认带来的满足。
and you can understand that your mind
大家明白脑子会把
mistakes the talking for the doing.
说的当成做的来替代。
But if you do need to talk about something,
但是如果你的确要谈论一些目标，
you can state it in a way
你说到这些目标时
that gives you no satisfaction,
不带有任何满足感，
such as, "I really want to run this marathon,
例如，“我的确想要跑马拉松，
so I need to train five times a week
所以我需要每周训练5次，
and kick my ass if I don't, okay?"
如果我做不到，就踢我的屁股吧？”
So audience, next time you're tempted to tell someone your goal,
所以观众们，下一次当你试图告诉别人你的目标时，
what will you say? (Silence)
你会说什么？
Exactly, well done.
完全正确，做对了。（对你的目标缄默，闭住嘴。保守秘密。）
(Applause)
（掌声）